<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>More Vanilla Biomes</name>
  <author>Zylle</author>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
	<li>1.5</li>
   </supportedVersions>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">GUI/ZModLogo</modIconPath>
   <packageId>zylle.MoreVanillaBiomes</packageId>
   <modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
</modDependencies>
  <description>
Features:
More Vanilla Biomes adds more map variety without overhauling the game. Includes eight new vanilla-friendly biomes.

Marsh: Marshy terrain with dense plants but few trees. Temperate to cold.

Grasslands: Warm, with poor soil, lots of grass, and few trees.

Coastal Dunes: Low-lying sandy area with lots of water. 

Sandbar: Smooth, flat, sandy islands with little if any vegetation or arable land.

Alpine Meadow: A beautiful area with fertile soil, lots of flowers, and few predators. The summers are mild and bountiful, and the winters are cold and harsh.

Oasis: Desert with groundwater close to the surface, making small lakes that support pockets thick vegetation.

Iceberg: Frigid chunks of ice floating on the ocean. Who would want to live here?

Cloud Forest: Found at the tops of tropical mountains and named for the constant fog. Animals frequently wander up the slopes from the forests below.

Badlands: Rocky, dry and desolate, these temperate regions feature little life.

Glacial Shield: Where the glacier meets the tundra, this area is icy, rocky, and cold almost year-round. Thick stands of forest are concentrated in patches of soil and around lakes, attracting wildlife.

-------------------------
Compatibility
This mod is meant to be as widely compatible as possible. Please report any issues.

If you use mods that add wild plants or animals, the new biomes will spawn modded plants and animals based on which vanilla biome(s) the plants and animals spawn in.

Compatible with other biome mods including Alpha Biomes, Advanced Biomes, Archipelagos,and Nature's Pretty Sweet.

Mods that change world generation may cause strange results, please report any issues.

Save Our Ship 2: I added More Vanilla Biomes to my 7-year ongoing game with 90 other mods and made settlements in two of the new biomes (coastal dunes and alpine meadows) on my second planet. Do this at your own risk, save first, and as always report any problems. 

Supports Camouflage and Stealth.

Fishing-- compatible with: 
Vanilla Fishing Expanded
FishIndustry
[RF] Fishing [1.0]

Recommended
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1095331978]Prepare Landing[/url] to help find the biome of your choice
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=761315214]Map Reroll[/url] if playing on maps without much solid ground.
Your choice of gravel visibility mod, especially if playing in Grasslands or Dunes. Some options are [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1613910454]Gravel[/url], [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1541281864]Where's the Gravel?[/url], and [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1561838700]Soil Contrast[/url]

Incompatibility
Terra Project: Makes extensive changes to world generation that I can't work around.

Please report any other incompatibilities you find.

-------------------------
Credits:
This mod uses code borrowed from [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1539309846]Rainbeau's Archipelagos[/url]

Translations:
Japanese by Proxyer 
French by DrTCS and qux
Simplified Chinese by 第四天灾

-------------------------
Links:
Get it on Github: https://github.com/Zylleon/MoreVanillaBiomes/releases/latest
Discord: https://discord.gg/CQrsbEV
My other mods: https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197998830956/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100

Support me: https://ko-fi.com/zylleon

	
	
</description>
</ModMetaData>